[{"answer": "Your girlfriend of two years breaks up with you right before New Year's Eve and all you can say is", "docId": "Yes-Man.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": " I can't believe I've been dating someone so emotionless", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "That would be inappropriate", "docId": "Yes-Man.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "C'mere. It'll be OK", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Only like fift", "docId": "Yes-Man.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Oh you do not. But you need it. And that's why you are here", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "I don't know if I want that", "docId": "Yes-Man.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Cool. Do you want anything from the refreshment area", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": " Excuse me, but we were here before those people", "docId": "Yes-Man.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Yes, we were", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "Yes-Man.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Where did you hear that", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "I'm going to miss you, baby", "docId": "Yes-Man.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "I can't watch you go", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "I just adopted her. If you're interested, they're giving them away in front of that place", "docId": "Yes-Man.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Neither did I", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "So, what do you say we hit this crazy party", "docId": "Yes-Man.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "White noise", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Is he scared to get married? Is that why he doesn't care", "docId": "Yes-Man.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "You know how to show it. A wedding is a huge deal. I'm so scared", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "I was kidding. Not as sexy as it seems. It gets in like everywhere.  What should we do to celebrate", "docId": "Yes-Man.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "How about Korean? Oh, no, you probably already had some today", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Have dinner", "docId": "Yes-Man.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": " No, we just had American food, American fare", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": " I think we're going to that place", "docId": "Yes-Man.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": " that place, that place, comrade", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": " that place, senorita", "docId": "Yes-Man.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": " that place", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "How've you been? You... never called", "docId": "Yes-Man.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Yeah, well, I've been busy too", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "How well off", "docId": "Yes-Man.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "I should know all the data", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": " You're a total con artist", "docId": "Yes-Man.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": " I've put my life into the hands of a con artist! And because of you I have this retarded yes branded on my hand for life!  This man is a con artist! Don't listen to this man! He is a con artist", "qsentId": 34}]